{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"1c0e1dbb-c922-4db7-9382-15629b060ed9"},"exam":{"id":"4a0e0b5f-6aa4-47a6-8edf-6ac9f0c904b2","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"el8zebxq-qo1d-az5o-l4lp-vmh132hnt1zd","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance guarantees attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US?","explanation":"A HIPAA certification attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"},{"url":"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hippa_(disambiguation)","title":"HIPPA or HIPAA"}],"answers":[{"id":"393dceb94f2cac456fd53985a67d72b3","text":"HITECH","correct":false},{"id":"827ec26130c30cc52e3fb178e0ef505c","text":"FERPA","correct":false},{"id":"d0a785d52ac4a841f7efdf0098d9ebd5","text":"HIPAA","correct":true},{"id":"dba5359496e7ea71f51ce4da1ee614bd","text":"GLBA","correct":false},{"id":"739f96badcfca6fd03c1e5b17971c9de","text":"HIPPO","correct":false}]},{"id":"2d6841a4-2163-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS, you can stop or terminate instances when not in use. Which of the following concepts describes this capability?","explanation":"Elasticity denotes the ability to increase or reduce the number or capabilities of AWS resources when needed. In this case, stopping or terminating instances means that you are reducing the number of AWS resources used in your environment.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"857defc5b4c6f1fef867a03c300bdd29","text":"Loose Coupling","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false}]},{"id":"a87b87a1-e801-e917-756a-a78256b2945c","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is a Shared Control of the AWS Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"Shared Controls are elements of the Shared Responsibility Model where both AWS and the customer have shared responsibilities within their own contexts. Awareness & Training is a Shared Control, since AWS trains AWS employees, but a customer must train their own employees. Datacentre Security is solely the responsibility of AWS. Configuration of an Application within an EC2 instance, and Identity and Access Management remain the responsibility of the customer","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"027e815b818f136c5892cd32b9f87ddd","text":"Awareness & Training","correct":true},{"id":"791716f366839a73d41b8ac1ae95bad0","text":"Identity and Access Management","correct":false},{"id":"e40133007bfa03149696a52e6c45b8d9","text":"EC2 Instance Application Configuration","correct":false},{"id":"4fde53f82fbc6748a0e6b9b51f615287","text":"Datacentre Security","correct":false}]},{"id":"alwhmkiv-aa40-zbsb-1app-zkbeiem7zvs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, for which of the following does AWS not assume responsibility?","explanation":"Customers are responsible for their own customer data in the cloud. AWS manages the Networking, Hypervisor Configuration, and Physical Security","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS shared Responsibility"}],"answers":[{"id":"1b837a3c0786d704da0c00c61b4d57b5","text":"Hypervisors","correct":false},{"id":"5dd5aedeaa5de8a95f383a8e014b1e5d","text":"Physical security of AWS facilities","correct":false},{"id":"a5fa5746370b608090b994a97b49e98b","text":"Networking","correct":false},{"id":"6016c2bb7bd8dd79293094d37ebfea3f","text":"Customer data","correct":true}]},{"id":"123bb9de-8d93-4feb-81c0-d4e85038cd47","domain":"tech","question":"When setting up the properties of an S3 bucket, which of the following options should you select to get detailed records for the requests made to the bucket?","explanation":"Server access logging is what you should select to record and get information on the requests made to your bucket. Object-level logging, sometimes referred to as S3 CloudTrail logging, saves all API events performed on the S3 bucket in json format.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/ServerLogs.html","title":"Amazon S3 Server Access Logging"}],"answers":[{"id":"30054ccc9b587d53668a89942396874c","text":"Server access logging","correct":true},{"id":"f87d839acefa86eff3c90b1b44be4aba","text":"Object-level logging","correct":false},{"id":"198a30920479d1d8e2509b9b59f3d700","text":"Versioning","correct":false},{"id":"189f63f277cd73395561651753563065","text":"Tags","correct":false}]},{"id":"5fd1imv7-lqes-7e9n-vz33-eau71532v2ly","domain":"security","question":"How does AWS Shield Standard help protect your environment?","explanation":"AWS Shield Standard is included at no extra cost but will only block DDOS attacks on your AWS resources - it will not scan the contents of incoming or outgoing traffic (this is a function of WAF) and will not protect your environment from viruses","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/shield-chapter.html","title":"AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"84009024e233c4995b00c514474f0ae5","text":"By Blocking DDOS attacks","correct":true},{"id":"3e6fc5c29a49e9d5c54bd4950ad5cbe0","text":"By scanning outgoing application traffic for sensitive information","correct":false},{"id":"55063c26653acc06bd00cc13e1acc3a4","text":"By scanning your instances for viruses","correct":false},{"id":"b1d6309ddb9cc2f856af5a3bab83f37e","text":"By scanning incoming application traffic for know attacks","correct":false}]},{"id":"425faace-2155-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"When you start using IAM, the service automatically creates your unique sign-in page URL. If your AWS Account ID is 'My_Account_02', which of the following URL links uses the correct format?","explanation":"Your sign-in page URL includes domain name elements in the following order – your AWS Account ID, and the phrases 'signin.aws.amazon.com' and 'console' to signify signing into the IAM Management Console. In addition, this URL uses the HTTPS protocol for secure communication, rather than HTTP.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/console.html","title":"The IAM Console and Sign-in Page"}],"answers":[{"id":"61949f1f3319a74075cd14016d668253","text":"http://My_Account_02.signin.aws.amazon.com/console/","correct":false},{"id":"9c70ec3408a767a41ecea94472be073e","text":"https://My_Account_02.signin.aws.amazon.com/console/","correct":true},{"id":"a2a7a98fc7b23032d2c5d56c2d81e321","text":"https://My_Account_02.sign-in.aws.amazon.com/console/","correct":false},{"id":"2b7795289d99d5ef8d59050dac917e90","text":"https://signin.aws.com/My_Account_02/","correct":false},{"id":"9012524a38ced0fcd61c8cb60c0f6f16","text":"http://console/sign-in.aws.com/My_Account_02/","correct":false},{"id":"a74366ac1b3fb89024e27fb049324d06","text":"https://signin.aws.com/console/My_Account_02/","correct":false}]},{"id":"7a194fa6-5966-4548-9b32-ac602a517ac8","domain":"concepts","question":"With AWS services, you can use as many resources as you need, as well as use them when you need them. Which of the following terms can be applied to this concept?","explanation":"Working in a traditional infrastructure environment means that you have to deal with fixed resources, which is comparatively costly and labor-intensive. By contrast, AWS services are much more convenient; the services provide the ability to use as many resources as you need and dispose of them when you no longer need them. That’s why such resources are both temporary and disposable.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"e035a6f9ed7c8c3c99e48b95e32cc364","text":"Fixed resources","correct":false},{"id":"83ec702ebd8e13f87318dba136356773","text":"Dedicated resources","correct":false},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true},{"id":"5936fc4450b6f3f75cc6fe08d2890b77","text":"Temporary resources","correct":true}]},{"id":"rv438cbg-ow9h-jrfd-gxxt-a83ko2ojlo7c","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS' Global Infrastructure, what are Edge Locations responsible for?","explanation":"Edge Locations host a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"7e293752730d983b3fb263bc37525a5c","text":"Hosting a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"e2dd2357c3f760b6df8cd9ef82402a0e","text":"Providing disaster recovery services","correct":false},{"id":"0df5575df91cfdc3471135f97cd57b5b","text":"Providing redundant backup to your AWS services","correct":false},{"id":"3d5bde6fd721f0872d6ad91a83e073cd","text":"Providing independent power grids to Availability Zones","correct":false}]},{"id":"96g9onz0-tv5t-sedb-7kg9-wv5k4uz50hgn","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is AWS' Data Warehousing service?","explanation":"Redshift is AWS' data warehousing service. Elastic Map Reduce is a large scale data processing service. Snowball is a physical appliance used to transfer data into, or out of AWS. S3 Big Data does not exist.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/redshift/latest/mgmt/welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon Redshift?"}],"answers":[{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":true},{"id":"6d5e386be8e0c962fec3431ac8198e82","text":"S3 Big Data","correct":false},{"id":"22ab04a992dc8483216fed8f9b932b77","text":"Elastic Map Reduce","correct":false},{"id":"c0429b6a658dd488f7262d983c7e02bb","text":"Snowball","correct":false}]},{"id":"lzz1xk7l-o7hw-05ld-eq4w-bnnsryn338qb","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below can be specified as an origin when creating a CloudFront distribution?","explanation":"A CloudFront Origin can be an S3 bucket, an Elastic Load Balancer, or a valid domain name.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/DownloadDistS3AndCustomOrigins.html","title":"CloudFront Origins"}],"answers":[{"id":"c0289d18d5fb07085b2755204da9008b","text":"A domain name","correct":true},{"id":"19c648650c3e65663a1edebcca84f065","text":"An ELB","correct":true},{"id":"c727fd87c3ae231f10b00f5df6719fdc","text":"An RDS instance","correct":false},{"id":"9cf4bd30d8e419d4586659b785653daf","text":"An S3 Bucket","correct":true}]},{"id":"86ed7d54-4495-435b-908a-b439c255c35d","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the five best practices does AWS Trusted Advisor use to eliminate unused, underutilized, and idle resources in your environment?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor ensures cost optimization of your AWS account by eliminating unused, underutilized, and idle resources, which include EC2 instances, load balancers, EBS volumes, and elastic IP addresses.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/best-practice-checklist/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor Best Practice Checks"}],"answers":[{"id":"a39ae09f8be4327fc176cfeb76a0e366","text":"Cost optimization","correct":true},{"id":"9446a98ad14416153cc4d45ab8b531bf","text":"Performance","correct":false},{"id":"45a75e44a713fdf94dbf1dbaa0749188","text":"Fault tolerance","correct":false},{"id":"2fae32629d4ef4fc6341f1751b405e45","text":"Security","correct":false},{"id":"07d2fdfae089a6e085811b22437de261","text":"Service limits","correct":false}]},{"id":"d18562b0-19ef-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"VPC, CloudFront, and Route 53 are examples of what type of AWS service?","explanation":"Amazon VPC, Amazon CloudFront, and Amazon Route 53 are networking and content delivery services that AWS offers. VPC and Route 53 are involved with linking resources with one another to operate interactively; VPC creates a virtual network, and Route 53 connects end users to web applications. CloudFront is an AWS service for fast web content delivery.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/latest/aws-overview/networking-services.html","title":"Networking and Content Delivery"}],"answers":[{"id":"e307db07b3975fef922a80d07455ee5e","text":"Database","correct":false},{"id":"a623a8d0366bf079411aa30be45b2d10","text":"Compute","correct":false},{"id":"57c28ff1fb9ea9b16bc846660a260623","text":"Networking and Content Delivery","correct":true},{"id":"e9a86c354aaf76a2e678148d3d2b9817","text":"Migration and Transfer","correct":false}]},{"id":"o8aqfsp4-kk6k-gyj7-frq7-4bpn7iv5zqm8","domain":"concepts","question":"You have a mission-critical application which must be globally available at all times. Which deployment strategy should you follow?","explanation":"A Multi-Region deployment will best ensure global availability. While it can be the most expensive, and complex to configure, Multi-Regional architectures will ensure that even if all Availability Zones in a single region fail due to a catastrophic event, your data will remain accessible.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"e4ec2833a31f482abfdb31691f0351dc","text":"Multi-Region","correct":true},{"id":"91d7ff212b9bda483701aeb4209ae5ec","text":"Deploy to all Availability Zones in your home region.","correct":false},{"id":"86b2c5243e03e210528f020bad4efdb9","text":"Multi-VPC in two AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"ec206762c0bea997a5b0f91783cce54f","text":"Multi-Availability Zone","correct":false}]},{"id":"5ca8852d-519a-409a-b998-d74eb78ef5cf","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are Amazon EFS (Elastic File Storage) storage classes?","explanation":"There are two Amazon EFS storage classes, which are Standard and Infrequent Access. One Zone – Infrequent Access, Intelligent Tiering, and Deep Glacier are names specifically for Amazon S3 storage classes.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/efs/latest/ug/whatisefs.html","title":"What Is Amazon Elastic File System?"}],"answers":[{"id":"72156eca90dac061dfd0a6da22c5e9b0","text":"Deep Glacier","correct":false},{"id":"13c28d56109c12a096b5e325b65a1c01","text":"Intelligent Tiering","correct":false},{"id":"eb6d8ae6f20283755b339c0dc273988b","text":"Standard","correct":true},{"id":"9f0832b6670166f059cfdc8dc49133b4","text":"One Zone - Infrequent Access","correct":false},{"id":"b1926a8ac417114ef193a282594538c7","text":"Infrequent Access","correct":true}]},{"id":"4885465a-c1a0-41e2-8e7d-d6ac27557522","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following comprises an Amazon Machine Image (AMI)?","explanation":"An AMI includes three types of information. There’s the Amazon EBS snapshot or snapshots for backing up EBS volume data to S3, or a template for the root volume of the instance if the AMI is instance-store-backed. There are launch permissions for controlling which AWS accounts can use the AMI to launch an instance. And there’s block device mapping for specifying the volumes to attach to the instance when it’s launched. These are the pieces of information that AMI requires to launch an EC2 instance; the EC2 instance is part of the AMI itself.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/WindowsGuide/AMIs.html","title":"Amazon Machine Images (AMI) – Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"11d5f5efdfcf29972a22321321560da7","text":"EBS snapshots or root volume template of an EC2 instance","correct":true},{"id":"fb7756bd7b1e9872836772b73ccf9aac","text":"Launch permissions","correct":true},{"id":"1dd2a814eff8bee8cf3e4da0ee6a245e","text":"Block device mapping","correct":true},{"id":"6f8a7b69b94bd2a5b6d397b35bf7a403","text":"EC2 instance","correct":false}]},{"id":"955c3d5e-7bce-4502-a765-a1b7883e6b42","domain":"billing","question":"Why would you use Tags in AWS?","explanation":"A tag is a label that you or AWS assigns to an AWS resource. You can use tags to organize your resources, and cost allocation tags to track your AWS costs on a detailed level.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html","title":"AWS Tags"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a83d3966af703cdd10973b715644342","text":"To store code","correct":false},{"id":"8fa9b4921f616acb2d005a4fb25ea9e2","text":"To organize your resources","correct":true},{"id":"3785763b04891a512dcbd1f190ddde7a","text":"To store passwords for your servers","correct":false},{"id":"881e2086647235f606ee190833b2b149","text":"For a No-SQL data store","correct":false}]},{"id":"bce6da84-1c95-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon which of these measurements is AWS Lambda pricing based?","explanation":"With AWS Lambda, you are charged based on the number of requests for your functions and the amount of time (duration) it takes for your code to execute.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/pricing/","title":"AWS Lambda Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"4789f23283b3a61f858b641a1bef19a3","text":"Memory","correct":false},{"id":"e02d2ae03de9d493df2b6b2d2813d302","text":"Duration","correct":true},{"id":"a817cbcc67f9a1988581b7d71d401622","text":"Number of requests","correct":true},{"id":"880a586b8b9c63efeba6c7f9afae7dc0","text":"Data transfer","correct":false}]},{"id":"464c8f56-20a3-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following types of EC2 instances is ideal for workloads that process large data sets in memory?","explanation":"True to its naming, memory optimized instances are specifically for workloads that require more memory than usual to process data.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/","title":"Amazon EC2 Instance Types"}],"answers":[{"id":"94a1a3953054d8ece597f4f69bb343d4","text":"General Purpose","correct":false},{"id":"2f925ef0b67b13f124d684b4e0ca9682","text":"Accelerated Computing","correct":false},{"id":"ea999a66bf3ccfec4616d5be49348665","text":"Storage Optimized","correct":false},{"id":"fb152ac1edfe96da5fe255e395003b0d","text":"Memory Optimized","correct":true},{"id":"b26f852f8cf53bd055d76deddcadf155","text":"Compute Optimized","correct":false}]},{"id":"cykf25tw-ja73-62pe-bg44-2xko23ptcj2t","domain":"security","question":"Broadly speaking AWS is responsible for:","explanation":"Generally speaking, AWS is responsible for security OF the cloud - meaning that it is responsible for the infrastructure (hardware and software) which is used to deliver cloud services to customers.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"e5a10169b294451720bbfc8cee548381","text":"Security both IN and OF the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"17e0b507a41c19ff7684c3bf9d56497f","text":"None of security - security is up to the customer to manage","correct":false},{"id":"2ac2679f0084e375060c216fe7477ab4","text":"Security OF the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"2245b1bb4da8871fd09d4b5b6c52555e","text":"Security IN the cloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"bcc6x5vm-wlrp-z3vu-k77q-nltdaem9w8ep","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is not database service in AWS?","explanation":"Amazon EBS is a storage service providing virtual hard disks in the cloud, while the other services listed are database services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/products/databases/","title":"AWS Databases"}],"answers":[{"id":"bacabc9e09c314ac47bb30bd2f431cf4","text":"Amazon Neptune","correct":false},{"id":"69670a9d53817d1ec89e685997343ce2","text":"Amazon Aurora","correct":false},{"id":"516729a7c0562425406a22cfe6a2c163","text":"Amazon EBS","correct":true},{"id":"f7415e33f972c03abd4f3fed36748f7a","text":"Amazon Redshift","correct":false}]},{"id":"w53824dy-uk0y-a0r6-b6eu-8t2xzl3155or","domain":"tech","question":"Yourself and a colleague both want to create a bucket called \"myawsomebucket\" to store your study notes - will you both be able to do this?","explanation":"As S3 bucket names are global, they need to be globally unique meaning you and your colleague cannot have two buckets with the same name, no matter the circumstances","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/Welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon S3?"}],"answers":[{"id":"e90d556314ed67ac2dcf70aa2bd7fefd","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Accounts","correct":false},{"id":"93cba07454f06a4a960172bbd6e2a435","text":"Yes","correct":false},{"id":"bafd7322c6e97d25b6299b5d6fe8920b","text":"No","correct":true},{"id":"3de7dd4f2d662d5eecc35fa4eadaa8c8","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Regions","correct":false}]},{"id":"aosxkeh9-qevj-zztz-qgkg-lo0glwr2ccoh","domain":"billing","question":"By default, when using consolidated billing, which of the below will the master paying account be able to do in the member account?","explanation":"By default, using Consolidated Billing only allows the master account to view the billing information from the member accounts - no access is automatically granted for users in the master account into the member accounts beyond this. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/consolidated-billing.html","title":"AWS Consolidated Billing"}],"answers":[{"id":"54e29f93505b20fe2cc8af1cce96a33b","text":"View any data stored","correct":false},{"id":"29f838d6149e7ff36b4692f879dbd0a3","text":"Grant access to member account to other users","correct":false},{"id":"3dbb078ea9c1eaf843d213ba217af3e8","text":"View billing information","correct":true},{"id":"25e6de5387e3157c014e2c6f2b0e810e","text":"Make changes to resources","correct":false}]},{"id":"6c02ad88-1feb-11ea-a32c-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon sign-up of an AWS account, how much Amazon DynamoDB storage will you get?","explanation":"When you sign up for an AWS account, you will get 25 GB of DynamoDB storage for the first 12 months under the AWS Free Tier.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"272aa49fa956677af70625391009423f","text":"25 GB","correct":true},{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false},{"id":"dcfebc6fbca2c5316f55c914e6593d2d","text":"100 GB","correct":false},{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":false}]},{"id":"q9rl4dzm-8wyq-y23f-41wx-15rhrz976akb","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are a collection of datacentres within a specific region?","explanation":"Availability Zones are a collection of datacentres within a specific region.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":false},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false}]},{"id":"1ad299fd-63d9-4a60-9949-d88b086002cf","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE when running a database in an EC2 Instance?","explanation":"In this case - as the database is being run in an EC2 instance, all aspects of database updates and access is the responsibility of the customer. Similarly as it is and EC2 instance, the customer is responsible for OS patching. Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which in this case is the EC2 instance - anything to do with the instance itself is the responsibility of the customer ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"42d5fd24fef6883fb899e3afd050b5a5","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":true},{"id":"0d6e04dd939a298f20dd927b2a10aa7c","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":false},{"id":"52f2eff0e91b46fe3007ca238393c185","text":"The customer is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"c7098373cbee0fc9617269a6d3765dd4","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"199f4eaff96b0da13d07770ee0ff2ab4","text":"AWS is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":false},{"id":"9f9f41256e31feca524f1209e25d70fa","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the database software","correct":true}]},{"id":"nfy6hmhv-trpt-lh3v-z6zh-4icv8kpv7xn6","domain":"concepts","question":"When setting up an Organization in AWS, which of the below is true when selecting which features to enable?","explanation":"With AWS Organizations, Consolidated Billing is always enabled. All other features are either enabled as a group, or disabled as a group - that is, you cannot individually enable or disable a feature - it's all or nothing!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/en_pv/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_getting-started_concepts.html","title":"AWS Organizations Terminology and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"ea31b0ef93ed02b05984774a32d72054","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, then pick which other individual features you want enabled ","correct":false},{"id":"125540f5091c07ae2a9b7b8c0d95a432","text":"You can select to have just Consolidated Billing enabled","correct":true},{"id":"fd07b14b5f6a4065154c418c232ecd89","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing disabled, then pick which of the other features you want enabled.","correct":false},{"id":"4890bb732d34952682735fd4950bcae8","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, plus all other features enabled","correct":true}]},{"id":"b7d5jc0p-zg8y-0hwp-3cjv-2yxp349xk58p","domain":"security","question":"You want to streamline access management for your AWS administrators by assigning them a pre-defined set of permissions based on their job role - which of the below is the best way to approach this?","explanation":"Using IAM Groups lets you create a list of pre-defined permissions that any user made a part of that group will be granted. Roles are primarily used to grant AWS resources permissions to other AWS resources and generally are not for end-users. Amazon Cognito is a service that help authenticate users to your apps, and not the AWS console itself.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_groups.html","title":"IAM Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"71f7b94ac76ec4aa2860353bc1120591","text":"Use IAM Roles","correct":false},{"id":"28639700aadbc704e3daae5ba44ab388","text":"Use Amazon Cognito","correct":false},{"id":"48fb6d39f4c7857dc342d789480a20ea","text":"Use AWS Organizations","correct":false},{"id":"ffc1a593680549bf1bc0e966a70f0683","text":"Use IAM Groups","correct":true}]},{"id":"pdd3afvz-mr6t-zycv-zdle-ceeorrmdl4o9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Risk and Compliance Program?","explanation":"Control Environment, Risk Management and Information Security are all components of the AWS Risk and Compliance Program. Control Environment includes policies, processes and control activities that are in place to secure the delivery of AWS’ service offerings. AWS management has developed a strategic business plan which includes risk identification and the implementation of controls to mitigate or manage risks as part of the Risk Management component. AWS has implemented a formal information security program designed to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of customers’ systems and data.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/compliance/AWS_Risk_and_Compliance_Whitepaper.pdf","title":"AWS Risk and Compliance"}],"answers":[{"id":"66216159eaf3a0abb2752836096f99e9","text":"Security Principles","correct":false},{"id":"791716f366839a73d41b8ac1ae95bad0","text":"Identity and Access Management","correct":false},{"id":"0719bdee85b7a37d4e74a9d542d24861","text":" Physical Security","correct":false},{"id":"74f53be5e22fad65f914f82977df2447","text":"Control Environment","correct":true},{"id":"b8aba77333d3fc881739506fee08811c","text":"Environment Automation","correct":false},{"id":"0889f4cee1d9f42ae2c1daf686377de0","text":"Information Security","correct":true},{"id":"7228bb53bb7855d458965d2f15fc6cd7","text":"Risk Management","correct":true}]},{"id":"6b870cda-5b5c-4de5-9270-86070c71041a","domain":"tech","question":"As an IT support center team member, you begin receiving calls from users about problems they’re experiencing with your company’s AWS-based point-of-sale system. You want to begin your investigation by checking with AWS for any service alerts they may be communicating. Which AWS tool will you give you the information you seek?","explanation":"The AWS Personal Health Dashboard publishes alerts and remediation guidance when issues with AWS services arise. Notifications are also provided for scheduled events that may impact AWS customers. Trusted Advisor provides valuable guidance for architecting your AWS environment and workloads, but doesn't include AWS service health information. The other two options are not tools offered by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/","title":"AWS Support Technology"}],"answers":[{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":false},{"id":"d189bb1b260dc3da48b6e6f5e1ec6879","text":"AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":true},{"id":"55b3625579acc4ff6b1d6d2bd4f3e7a8","text":"AWS Operations Monitor","correct":false},{"id":"24379bc91642f36debad3a12e0407c26","text":"AWS Global Status Center","correct":false}]},{"id":"9635210d-5701-4697-a1c1-43d560757b8f","domain":"billing","question":"When would you use the EC2 On Demand pricing model?","explanation":"You would use the EC2 On Demand model when you need compute capability that does not require any up front payments or long term commitments, and where you have applications with short term or unpredictable workloads that cannot be interrupted.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"6f30c21b296170a18a7b5b51e1b41463","text":"Guaranteed cost","correct":false},{"id":"745e16b69cf097a0be4ccb8e3a7e1a39","text":"Discounted cost model compared to Reserved Instances ","correct":false},{"id":"e6f9ef5372dbb1435dcf5572384518a0","text":"No upfront payments required","correct":true},{"id":"fd379e462843bd9411eeb4d620576dae","text":"Unpredictable workloads that cannot be interrupted","correct":true}]},{"id":"04uew9ya-7pbn-ugmi-3vzh-1erxijop26v7","domain":"billing","question":"You are an AWS Enterprise customer with questions about billing and your overall AWS account. Which of the following AWS support personnel should you contact?","explanation":"For AWS Enterprise customers, the AWS Concierge is a resource dedicated to answering billing and account questions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/features/","title":"AWS Support Features"}],"answers":[{"id":"26e8220e8fac28d2a1a9a18ca81aabd7","text":"AWS Support","correct":false},{"id":"bac90b5cd782c7dc092efa042af32e5c","text":"AWS Concierge","correct":true},{"id":"0037cad42801741c9acb59d7d7ba9a5f","text":"AWS Billing and Accounts","correct":false},{"id":"aebccaafe1827e1ed91b1d9a27dac4a8","text":"AWS Technical Account Manager","correct":false}]},{"id":"11cddf60-2bb5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services is an example of Platform as a Service?","explanation":"Platform as a Service, or PaaS, enables the development, running, and management of applications on the cloud without the need to build and maintain any infrastructure. That is precisely what Elastic Beanstalk provides; the ability to quickly deploy and manage applications in the AWS Cloud without worrying about the infrastructure that runs those applications. Elastic Beanstalk is the only PaaS listed here.","links":[{"url":"https: //aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/","title":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/types-of-cloud-computing/","title":"Types of Cloud Computing"}],"answers":[{"id":"dee7ff8f7b10b9d388c7c561e9413b0d","text":"AWS Lambda","correct":false},{"id":"bcf6eb183b7da148701bcc059a34675f","text":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"270fcb785810d0206945029bb05f4e97","text":"Amazon S3","correct":false},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"b9e84187-a101-b202-89a5-c5882d80f712","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is a Shared Control of the AWS Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"Shared Controls are elements of the Shared Responsibility Model where both AWS and the customer have shared responsibilities within their own contexts. Patch Management is a Shared Control, since AWS is responsible for patching and fixing flaws within the infrastructure, including managed services like RDS, but customers are responsible for patching their guest OS and applications. Firmware Upgrades, and other Hardware maintenance processes are solely the responsibility of AWS. Configuration of Security Groups remain the responsibility of the customer","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"c57c1a92dac4991db4fa1bca1517cca0","text":"Hardware Maintanence","correct":false},{"id":"474eabe8590389108f1fc92c9435c405","text":"Security Group Configuration","correct":false},{"id":"9ce46290f3196adff1535137f5fc1ee9","text":"Firmware Upgrades","correct":false},{"id":"5d8e5aef41d3dab7bda43eaace3a2a06","text":"Patch Management","correct":true}]},{"id":"2df4774c-2e69-4156-96c5-b1efbfba754f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. This means there will always be more AZs than Regions. Edge locations are separate from AZs and Regions, and there are more Edge Locations than Regions and Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"f35fa3c5e765907efd6efa66bc1741c3","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Regions","correct":false},{"id":"26c658a3c4aee0122f0178a65f0ea80b","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Regions","correct":true},{"id":"f4b49cc5b3d286cd78cac99f03cecce3","text":"There are more Regions than Availability zones","correct":false},{"id":"29030db1d3f86fea8d8779a9c964c207","text":"There are more Availability Zones than Edge locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"rku8juy8-m8eo-xhrd-ap7e-a3nhr9045k2l","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below is TRUE when considering subnets in a VPC?","explanation":"By default, all subnets within a VPC can communicate with each other, without needing any other resources or configuration. NAT Gateway and Internet Gateway work in different scenarios to allow your subnet to communicate with the internet and are not required to communicate between subnets","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/VPC_Subnets.html","title":"VPCs and Subnets"}],"answers":[{"id":"bdcce4ddcc3bbe6bca2d1851d91ff3a2","text":"By default, all subnets within a VPC can communicate with each other","correct":true},{"id":"b5bcf23beb0bab6ed020ef6e8d9026ef","text":"Subnets within a VPC can only communicate with each other if a NAT Gateway is deployed","correct":false},{"id":"ecfdf4b74c36d8d497f1023a5b24e38f","text":"Subnets within a VPC can only communicate with each other if an Internet Gateway is deployed","correct":false},{"id":"8ff25f40e9a121e4620e1809190ac599","text":"By default, subnets within a VPC cannot communicate with each other","correct":false}]},{"id":"d29bb03a-1a55-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for? (Choose 3)","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services. Such services include Amazon VPC, which enables a customer to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud. This section is simply referred to as a virtual private cloud, or VPC. So, while AWS is responsible for the software (Amazon VPC), the customer is responsible for the virtual network created with that software (VPC), as well as whatever goes in it. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses) and security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic).","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/what-is-amazon-vpc.html","title":"What Is Amazon VPC?"}],"answers":[{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true},{"id":"452be8d0a4b871d9b4ec8f7e323a17a2","text":"Virtual Private Clouds (VPCs)","correct":true},{"id":"1d7c6a62b7a045346e19186c911b38a1","text":"Amazon VPC Service","correct":false}]},{"id":"aaa7dqnz-f7nv-g9bl-zfw2-2xko23ptcj2t","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for managing when storing data in S3?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance). When it comes to S3, the customer is responsible for all aspects of the data being stored on S3, and who has access to manage the S3 service for that account","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"6c507c7b28d852214aa62ba95c5c7009","text":"Who has access to data you stored on the S3 Service","correct":true},{"id":"f661780dbe84a95f44f8622698e4b2a9","text":"Who has access to the S3 Infrastructure Software","correct":false},{"id":"2f6823eab5248af1500c3b8329fab352","text":"Who has access to the S3 Service","correct":true},{"id":"ae48532652716e286fa0be350d5545e3","text":"Who has access to the storage hardware","correct":false},{"id":"3278fa01d394d47605876669eaea2957","text":"Who has access to the network hardware","correct":false}]},{"id":"eaf197bf-a9f1-4611-90be-dbcf7364c74a","domain":"concepts","question":"You have an application load balancer for routing traffic from developers to the EC2 instance that contains a web application being put into operation. To prepare for the application going live for public use, you add an Auto Scaling Group and a second application load balancer to route web traffic from customers to the EC2 instance. The addition is an example of which of the following:","explanation":"This is an example of scalability, which means that systems are expected to grow over time with no drop in performance. ","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"2166e76dc88d642260416a536b06a412","text":"Durability","correct":false},{"id":"820b8f74ad843d1574106ec4cadfc07e","text":"Reliability","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true}]},{"id":"b6f1e02c-1a49-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS CloudTrail?","explanation":"CloudTrail is actually enabled automatically when you create an AWS account. The other three responses are correct.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awscloudtrail/latest/userguide/how-cloudtrail-works.html","title":"How CloudTrail Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"c4817f75e8865468e0d6688b3f7fa9ae","text":"CloudTrail delivers log files within 15 minutes of account activity.","correct":true},{"id":"38105bf4ed77d230d01428de259f3ea0","text":"By default, CloudTrail event log files are encrypted using Amazon S3 server-side encryption.","correct":true},{"id":"98be3a0e01d49274c41618e1b43ff9c5","text":"When you create an AWS account, you will have to manually enable CloudTrail.","correct":false},{"id":"d70f308061c9f3b0aef10fe5b3a954ab","text":"With CloudTrail, you can create a trail that either applies to one Region or to all Regions.","correct":true}]},{"id":"b04194cb-7c18-41fd-af07-af547fcdf3df","domain":"security","question":"A consulting firm is conducting a Sarbanes-Oxley compliance audit of your IT operations. The auditor requests visibility to logs of event history across your AWS-based employee expense system infrastructure. Which AWS service will record and provide give you the information you need?","explanation":"AWS CloudTrail provides visibility to API call activity for AWS infrastructure and other services. AWS Cloudwatch Logs might be part of a centralized logging solution, but all API event information will come from CloudTrail. AWS Systems Manager can process EC2 logs only, and AWS Compliance Manager is not a service offered by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/?nc2=h_m1","title":"AWS CloudTrail"}],"answers":[{"id":"28408acf54ab04fe847fd24957e528d9","text":"AWS CloudWatch Logs","correct":false},{"id":"26ca9b29af36f84c577a85a80a58a381","text":"AWS CloudTrail","correct":true},{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"811708e04896b95951b61e58635cc92d","text":"AWS Compliance Manager","correct":false}]},{"id":"zlyf2s8s-kula-sxtl-s07a-i3uh455n1hnu","domain":"security","question":"Which credentials can you use to access the AWS Management console?","explanation":"You use a username and password to log into the AWS console, although Access key and Secret Access key can be used to access some APIs programmatically","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/console/","title":"The AWS Management Console"}],"answers":[{"id":"be677306ceb7d966e7a06ee1bf387acf","text":"Your Access key","correct":false},{"id":"2a7454c71a60c06ab2189283f1788e09","text":"Your Secret Access key","correct":false},{"id":"afc76c6d8222878e0449abb2ea16838f","text":"Your Username and Password","correct":true},{"id":"4dd4dfb52929ef230415ada1a4169dc1","text":"Your Security Token","correct":false}]},{"id":"wvxqbzjc-c9jk-sld7-d5mu-q6zpjrfydg47","domain":"tech","question":"You have just created a new bucket and uploaded a file into it - will this be automatically viewable by anyone on the internet?","explanation":"By default, all data stored in S3 is NOT viewable by the public. If you want a bucket or object to be accessible by the public, you must explicitly make it so. NAT Gateways and Internet Gateways are needed to allow communications between VPCs and the internet, but are not required when it comes to S3","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/faqs/#security","title":"S3 Security"}],"answers":[{"id":"a8500b13e7e4474d341e354692b3af26","text":"Only if you have a NAT Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"7b30b72e7721523c1467f2387b5fa089","text":"Yes - by default buckets and their contents are public","correct":false},{"id":"7e6adeafa366013b86b4a4bea96c16ef","text":"Only if you have an Internet Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"c206c641ffd27b5062ee0b0d61cac9a5","text":"No - by default buckets and their contents are private","correct":true}]},{"id":"1cfba8e0-0fb8-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"You have EC2 and RDS instances, Redshift and Elasticsearch clusters, and an SNS topic in your AWS environment. Which of these services support reserved pricing?","explanation":"Amazon SNS is the only one of the five mentioned services that does not have reserved pricing. On the other hand, Amazon EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch do.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/pricing/","title":"Amazon Redshift Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticsearch-service/pricing/","title":"Amazon Elasticsearch Service Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"3ec389f2e16e0e0443f3ef49d2b58d05","text":"EC2 and RDS","correct":false},{"id":"9d6fbf729ccc02278cc50176a91ed3fe","text":"EC2, Redshift, and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"fcb02ff285a97f0ed386c6cfe36b02f4","text":"EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch","correct":true},{"id":"65e4dd05e0a1392e55661f27717e96cb","text":"RDS, Redshift, Elasticsearch, and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"0221d4f5950f35dfcf98f6a60f60d20d","text":" Elasticsearch and SNS","correct":false}]},{"id":"og6hjhzz-5hd0-yz2y-lhcp-id573kosdzz0","domain":"security","question":"When talking about AWS security, what does \"Authentication\" refer to?","explanation":"Authentication identifies who is accessing the system and passes that information to the authorization process, which in turn determines what permissions the user has in AWS. Although Authentication is the first part of the process to log in to the console, by itself it it is not enough.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/manage-users/","title":"Managing Users with IAM"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html","title":"IAM - authenticated vs. authorized "}],"answers":[{"id":"2fd83b869d1e9b4e9cb436b10c4dd876","text":"Logging in to the console","correct":false},{"id":"14f566a413faf99b530a23db8794522d","text":"A user delegating access to another user temporarily","correct":false},{"id":"0159ee609574fa72f3ce74e9f9acae98","text":"Evaluating what permissions a user has","correct":false},{"id":"1f8db5b38e9eb894bac42c8cfcc958a8","text":"Identifying who is accessing the system","correct":true}]},{"id":"pjzmsz8b-2lx2-8zb8-wauh-od1x4h0ja4pd","domain":"tech","question":"A new System Administrator has started with your organisation and requires a user account so that they can manage you AWS resources. You have AWS resources in multiple regions - what needs to be done to allow the new starter access to manage resources in the regions you operate in?","explanation":"Any answer that suggest a role is incorrect as roles by themselves will not let a user log in. The correct approach is to create an IAM user - and as IAM is a global service - configuration in IAM applies globally, not just regionally, only a single IAM user account is required.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html","title":"What is IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"2effe9ac093a8dcafdd02f3e97c1244e","text":"Create a single IAM role - this will enable access in all regions","correct":false},{"id":"98cddae0b6f5dfe1792d38678a9851a0","text":"Create an IAM role in each region that you have resources in - this will enable access in per region","correct":false},{"id":"15ed84de219d4333fe7069904bec4dbc","text":"Create an IAM user account in each region that you have resources in - this will enable access in per region","correct":false},{"id":"f854b98dd0b3ff05864e11c45979706b","text":"Create a single IAM user account - this will enable access in all regions","correct":true}]},{"id":"8ae68d9e-7bf8-41c2-996a-a01fb1bf966a","domain":"billing","question":"Which tool can help you to compare the cost of hosting resources in AWS vs the cost of hosting in a traditional data centre?","explanation":"The TCO calculators allow you to estimate the cost savings when using AWS and provide a detailed set of reports.  Pricing Calculator can be used to estimate potential AWS spend, and AWS Budgets & Billing Alarms can help keep spend under control by alerting you when you breach a threshold.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","title":"AWS TCO Calculator"}],"answers":[{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":false},{"id":"6b6f2097ec6555c2e09b7ed23571b3c5","text":"AWS Billing Alarms","correct":false},{"id":"1a98a10ad310a9ed66414dd3acb48e72","text":"AWS Pricing Calculator","correct":false},{"id":"e84e1dd83afcda636af8a6ae32a58cef","text":"AWS TCO Calculator","correct":true}]},{"id":"2cp5w12s-zexu-46ts-0im3-vuthjxgjujs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used?","explanation":"Elasticity describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"fb76c61f626c7fb0fd2ee1226e9fd8bd","text":"Fault-tolerance","correct":false}]},{"id":"1638290e-2fb4-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following does AWS use to notify you by email when you exceed 85% of your Free Tier limits for each service?","explanation":"AWS uses Budgets to notify you when you exceed 85% of your Free Tier limits for each service you’re using by sending you an email. Picking Cost Explorer as the answer is misleading; it is actually a visualizer you can use to analyze your spend, but it does not alert you on your Free Tier usage. Organizations centralizes the management of your resources; it has nothing to do with usage alerts. And Personal Health Dashboard allows you to visualize the status, rather than usage, of your resources.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/tracking-free-tier-usage.html","title":"Tracking Your Free Tier Usage"}],"answers":[{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":true},{"id":"b1820ee1cf68e2e65f263ff7bb207626","text":"AWS Organizations","correct":false},{"id":"c7f176d72688fd87853e31b84159d541","text":"AWS Cost Explorer","correct":false},{"id":"d189bb1b260dc3da48b6e6f5e1ec6879","text":"AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false}]},{"id":"812wx3ht-7wy1-12kp-ow6n-k8a1y15t2w6v","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below are common use cases for S3?","explanation":"Common use cases for Amazon S3 include storing application assets and static web hosting. AWS does not recommend using S3 for filesystems or for database storage.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/gsg/S3-gsg-CommonUseScenarios.html","title":"S3 Use Cases"}],"answers":[{"id":"28cbd7a2db3e5bd8ca1ba00ac2e966a8","text":"Storing application assets","correct":true},{"id":"181f55b567c0f81904aac0d8deeb5e17","text":"Static web hosting","correct":true},{"id":"484bf39587ca9f0fed0666ab7d34543a","text":"Hosting a relational database","correct":false},{"id":"f920ea13fb606314d3259470cdc8d429","text":"Installing a filesystem","correct":false}]},{"id":"918c058b-8c3d-4858-aa1b-de986b3379af","domain":"security","question":"Which following statement is true of newly created security groups with their default rules?","explanation":"By default, new security groups start with only an outbound rule to allow all traffic to leave the instances. You must add rules to enable any inbound traffic.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/VPC_SecurityGroups.html","title":"Security Groups for Your VPC"}],"answers":[{"id":"d00cd55aa36c87aedb13b4c0829aa462","text":"New security groups block both incoming and outbound traffic.","correct":false},{"id":"66152806bd7636ccc1a33303917cdddd","text":"New security groups allow only outbound traffic and block all incoming traffic.","correct":true},{"id":"d21ab4dffc222de4dfe6fddddca20b1f","text":"New security groups allow both incoming and outbound traffic.","correct":false},{"id":"8fbe4c39dc7d852a0b8aaa5b889b1ff1","text":"New security groups block outbound traffic and allow all incoming traffic.","correct":false}]},{"id":"7b242f9e-5541-40b9-94c3-ff760252f026","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following scenarios are examples of scaling an IT architecture vertically?","explanation":"To scale vertically is to increase the specifications of a single AWS resource as needed. For example, resizing EC2 or RDS instances for more CPU, memory, or network capabilities is scaling vertically. Adding more EC2 or RDS instances, on the other hand, is scaling horizontally because it involves the increase in the number of resources, rather than the increase in each resource’s capabilities.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"f9de222cea376a61a621e215c4daf0dc","text":"Resizing an RDS instance type from db.r5.large to db.r5.2xlarge","correct":true},{"id":"67c96e88044c732523807882de714af3","text":"Adding two more RDS instances","correct":false},{"id":"4fd553484e87f00281d8e2d07df1c3ac","text":"Resizing an EC2 instance type from a1.medium to a1.xlarge for more CPU and memory power","correct":true},{"id":"d2ed8876ad5d876850ebcde76e28bd9f","text":"Adding two more EC2 instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"2o4xzter-rc6s-wz14-cd0x-5ymcmahyoj0q","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an EC2 instance on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, EC2 patching is a Shared Control - AWS is responsible for the underlying hardware, but you as the user is responsible for patching the OS and Applications running in your instance","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"b8a5da87a2cdeca59f9782e25182f574","text":"Patching the applications","correct":true},{"id":"ce74e3a1c22bccb58acc0062f43153bd","text":"Patching the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"92d4ae83f773c1e79ec7ae29b20fa481","text":"Patching the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"3e164c265c82649647e641e322d93aa7","text":"Patching the operating system","correct":true}]},{"id":"075e3cda-4e62-4381-bb3f-0cd061c73bb3","domain":"security","question":"A purchasing department staff member is setup as an AWS user in the company’s procurement AWS account. At each month-end, the staff member needs access to an application running on EC2 in the company’s accounts payable AWS account to reconcile reports. Which of the following provides the most secure and operationally efficient way to give the staff member access to the accounts payable application?","explanation":"The staff member should be given the ability to assume a role programmatically with the permissions necessary to run the accounts payable application. Setting up another AWS user for the staff member in the accounts payable account will require the presentation of hard credentials programmatically. Both federation and Lambda will require the use of a role as well, but with the added overhead of maintaining Active Directory or the Lambda function.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_common-scenarios.html","title":"Common Scenarios for Roles: Users, Applications, and Services"}],"answers":[{"id":"926f9b540e5d5ff596976f059a7c9cbf","text":"Create a user for the staff member in the accounts payable AWS account","correct":false},{"id":"e9c43624dba6130e04955aabf167b8b2","text":"Have the user request temporary security credentials for the application by assuming a role","correct":true},{"id":"ecd3e317cda9a34ab820e6d6ff70fcf5","text":"Invoke an AWS Lambda function to run the application in the accounts payable AWS account","correct":false},{"id":"00383ff55511da79680a3cfdf7bd7a1b","text":"Configure Active Directory integration so that you can federate the staff member’s access to the accounts payable AWS account","correct":false}]},{"id":"69916ab3-c78a-4abd-86a8-5dc73e90916a","domain":"tech","question":"Your manager approaches you this morning to tell you there has been a surprise audit announced by the internal audit team for all of your company's AWS Accounts. Which service would you use to provide the necessary information to the audit team?","explanation":"AWS CloudTrail is a service that enables governance, compliance, operational and risk auditing of your AWS account.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/","title":"AWS CloudTrail"}],"answers":[{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"1aa2d5ab75afef6fa4ccd1e3b22174d4","text":"QuickSight","correct":false},{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":true},{"id":"9deb03cd21d41a691cdc24bfaab2820c","text":"Inspector","correct":false}]},{"id":"d05a0228-8d82-4cef-8dfb-4e2cb3856a9f","domain":"security","question":"According to the Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is AWS responsible for?","explanation":"Protecting the infrastructure that runs all of the services in the AWS Cloud is the responsibility of AWS. Such services include EC2 infrastructure - the hardware compute platform for running EC2 instances and Amazon Virtual Private Cloud, or VPC, which enables customers to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud to launch their resources. The subnets, security groups, and network access control lists configured in the VPC are the responsibility of the customer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/vpc/","title":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":true},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"28aaf85b7ba1e63aa22c1c645a4c22e4","text":"Elastic Cloud Compute (EC2) infrastructure","correct":true},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":false}]},{"id":"f81195c4-7959-4925-a41d-e50f901cccad","domain":"tech","question":"Your System Administration team lead wants you to subscribe to the RSS feed to be notified of any interruptions to the EC2 service in the N. California and Ohio Regions. Which of the following will enable you to do that?","explanation":"Service Health Dashboard displays the general status of AWS services, such as EC2, and it enables RSS subscription. The Personal Health Dashboard does provide information about the services you're using, but it does not give you the ability to subscribe to RSS feeds.","links":[{"url":"https://status.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Service Health Dashboard"}],"answers":[{"id":"cf4db9f312542c8284a6ccdefcd98544","text":"Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"087edf830b5f3b392ebaef37ba8550f7","text":"EC2 Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"8e75b153e61c22a8ea4e14aadc7cb4ee","text":"Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"5b60dd28958c0d6d59a455cc074e4322","text":"Service Health Dashboard","correct":true}]},{"id":"5a168390-1f66-11ea-a5e8-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"You added a recently hired HR Assistant to the IAM group named 'HumanResources'. Which of the following statements will apply to that user?","explanation":"By adding the HR Assistant to the 'HumanResources' group by using the AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) service, the new hiree is now a member of the company’s HR department and inherits the administrative permissions of that group.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/getting-started_create-admin-group.html","title":"Create Your First IAM Admin User and Group"}],"answers":[{"id":"367051fc494f2dba53682af0d5f9a9e1","text":"The HR Assistant becomes the AWS root account user.","correct":false},{"id":"4f98907d2b5e12fad173f30f4d61ec84","text":"The HR Assistant inherits the permissions of the 'HumanResources' group.","correct":true},{"id":"b098a137cb3a11528e46deb8c5aff98d","text":"The HR Assistant becomes an IAM member of the company’s Human Resources department.","correct":true},{"id":"a445a3cad5d84550114916ae6df763c4","text":"The HR Assistant becomes leader of the Human Resources department.","correct":false}]},{"id":"ff57921e-2faa-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following statements are true of the AWS Free Tier?","explanation":"All statements listed here are correct except for one. If you don’t use all your Free Tier benefits within the month, they don’t roll over to the next month.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-free-tier.html","title":"Using the AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"e0a5844f80154f67479f312499e75d1a","text":"Usage must be kept below the Free Tier limits to avoid charges.","correct":true},{"id":"8723f65debe98902ae71daeac7ca33e0","text":"Upon creation of an AWS account, the user is automatically signed up for the Free Tier for 12 months.","correct":true},{"id":"aec630c6387bfee54b18d0ca80ea994c","text":"Unused benefits that the Free Tier provides in a given month roll over to the next month.","correct":false},{"id":"fca0d4d0e7ba8ff0a86efa806423c98d","text":"AWS starts charging the regular rates for usage of services and resources when the Free Tier expires.","correct":true}]},{"id":"fde3bfdf-a9fa-4476-b785-b8de7b315aeb","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following languages can be used to author CloudFormation templates?","explanation":"CloudFormation supports both JavaScript Object Notation (JSON) and YAML Ain't Markup Language (aka YAML) for authoring CloudFormation templates.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSCloudFormation/latest/UserGuide/working-with-templates-cfn-designer-json-editor.html","title":"Integrated JSON and YAML Editor"}],"answers":[{"id":"a7f5f35426b927411fc9231b56382173","text":"Python","correct":false},{"id":"0ecd11c1d7a287401d148a23bbd7a2f8","text":"JSON","correct":true},{"id":"9463f87bbed1fcdacfb8d40e185ca2bc","text":"YAML","correct":true},{"id":"2a52ba6e26e550c59e15affa051e478b","text":"CAMEL","correct":false}]},{"id":"48f2d351-b6b2-4615-a662-be8ca8a2b84f","domain":"tech","question":"Trusted Advisor is classified as what type of AWS service?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor is a Management and Governance tool. It guides you on how to best manage your resources based on AWS best practices in five categories.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Documentation"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"a623a8d0366bf079411aa30be45b2d10","text":"Compute","correct":false},{"id":"5525aee13c9e8a25b1f35514f33ab825","text":"Security, Identity, and Compliance","correct":false},{"id":"458f5f8faf1e6121d97d167d4f94db24","text":"Management & Governance","correct":true},{"id":"c784a652acefe771f7a2853db61a07ae","text":"Application Integration","correct":false}]},{"id":"ef32cbf3-49b8-406a-aa2d-eaff05300839","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are separate from Regions and AZs. The number of Edge Locations around the world is greater than that of Regions and Availability Zones, in order to reduce latency between your content and your customers - the more that exist, the greater the chance there is one where you need it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"5810cb8fea9cc8e7773f9cc96fdd6c51","text":"There are more Regions than Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"78f3c24434277d629cc0a0d14f18c598","text":"There are more Edge locations than Availability zones","correct":true},{"id":"9fe244cde3895fdb2a60650e6154c15b","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"b8ecf41dfa2a8f2d576a9407c87dadf5","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Edge Locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"1978e26b-04e4-45ca-8a47-205e50d96c7f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are seperate from Regions and AZs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"988326895b235b7a5f2b7eea1a9838f5","text":"Regions contain Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"22d0cb7092012aea1123fcbd58c6519c","text":"Data Centres contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"23b72701776466936b717d47eb3be164","text":"Availability Zones contain Data Centres","correct":true},{"id":"cd6f4614de9281b97b511a1f3f534e8c","text":"Edge Locations contain Availability Zones","correct":false}]},{"id":"27ohq41k-k7qp-a4r2-2r7m-05za454l4hk3","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support levels offers 24x7 support via phone or chat?","explanation":"The Business and Enterprise support plans, the two most expensive plans, offer 24 X 7 support via phone or chat. Neither of the other support plans (Basic and Developer) offer Phone support. Individual is also not a real support plan","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true}]},{"id":"80c462fa-2fa6-11ea-aec2-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support plans provide access to online self-paced labs for training staff?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan provides access to online self-paced labs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false}]}]}}}}
